I don't look strange, do I?
The beginner's lunchbox making
Daily recipes
Food to make him happy
Don't go, my non-existent future
だから行かないで、僕のいない未来
dakara ikanaide, boku no inai mirai
I still haven't forgotten the feelings of that moment
あの一瞬の思いはまだ忘れない
ano isshun no omoi wa mada wasurenai
The word engraved deep in my heart ever since that day
あの日胸の奥握り締めた言葉
ano hi mune no oku nigirishimeta kotoba
That one single word changed my tomorrow
あの一言が明日を変えてくれたんだね
ano hitokoto ga ashita o kaete kuretan da ne
I'm watching a dream
僕は夢を見てる
boku wa yume o miteru
I wonder if it's my own dream
それは僕だけの夢かな
sore wa boku dake no yume kana
You're watching the sky
君は空を見てる
kimi wa sora o miteru
It's your own sky
それは君だけの空
sore wa kimi dake no sora
Once, just once
一つだけ　一つだけ
hitotsu dake hitotsu dake
As long as we hold what's important in our hearts
大切なもの胸にあれば
taisetsuna mono mune ni areba
We can get through both grief and endless nights
長い夜も嘆きも越えられるだろう
nagai yoru mo nageki mo koerareru darou
Just once, alone with you
一度だけ　君とだけ
ichido dake kimi to dake
These controversial dreams are all I have
かもした夢が僕の全て
kamoshita yume ga boku no subete
Cleared of my life, my desire to protect you remains
命を解け君を守りたい強く思う
inochi o toke kimi o mamoritai tsuyoku omou
This is the feeling I now call love
こんな気持ちを今愛と呼べろ
konna kimochi o ima ai to yobero
Saito-san.
「The 《moon》 sways by the poolside」
Saito Himea-san?
Is she on the rooftop again?
She did enter the classroom this morning.
Again? She's so annoying.
Saito-san never attends class, does she?
I guess she really does get special treatment.
Himea...
I wonder if class will be over soon.
That was over way too fast.
I didn't expect it to end like this after nine years.
I guess that's why I'm a genius.
Man, I'm starving!
We'll have to hurry, or they'll run out of croquette bread!
You scum! Do you think it's smart to get between me and my meal?
Mirai!
Whoa! What's that?
A bug? It's a huge bug, isn't it?
What's going on? What are you doing?
But... doing it out of the blue like that...
The curse is gone!
Mirai of Andu is now fully functional!
Get rid of that thing!
Okay, time for lunch.
Say, Taito. Are you buying bread at the cafetera again today?
Um, I was wondering if you were going to buy croquette bread for lunch at the cafeteria.
For lunch? Yeah, I thought about getting some.
You see, today I just happened to wake up early.
So I was like "Okay, time to make some lunch!"
But I ended up making a bit too much.
So I made lunch for you too!
Seriously?
It's like he's two-timing with Saito-san!
Kurogane-kun is so mean!
Kurogane-kun is a female's worst enemy!
He's so going down!
Poor Haruka.
Thank me later and dig in!
Is Taito here?
Let's have lunch together again!
Gekkou gave me some money,
so I bought some croquette bread!
Himea...
No, this is, um...
I'm dead. I'm so dead.
Hey, Taito. Where do you want to eat today?
On the bench at the courtyard? Or maybe on the roof?
Uh, you know... Um, Himea...
Wait, time-out!
Annoying Idiot Gekkou
Hello? What is it?
Get over here right now.
Huh? Why should I?
This isn't really the best time to be asking questions.
Don't you understand what I'm saying, small fry?
Who are you calling a small fry?!
You of course, who else?
Quit screwing around! And why do I have to follow your orders anyway?
A slave's job is to follow his master's orders.
You put me on the student council without my consent!
I didn't ask for your opinion.
You ass. Who the hell do you think you are?
A genius.
Damn that Gekkou!
I-Is that so? Now that's troubling, Kurenai-kun.
I understand. I'll be there in a jiffy.
Sorry, Haruka. The student council president called for me.
He said some urgent stuff came up.
Thanks for the lunch. I'll eat it later.
Oh, I see...
Now that you mention it, you're on the student council now, huh?
I guess there's nothing we can do about, since it's for the student council and all.
Y-Yeah! Work just keeps piling up!
C-Come on, Himea!
What? What's up?
This stuff called croquette bread is delicious!
I always thought human food was uncouth and disgusting, but I love everything that you've shown me, Taito!
Himea.
When we defeated Hinata,
I supposedly died, didn't I?
A message to all students.
Due to an inspection of the schoolfacilities,
all of today's afternoon classes and club activities are canceled.
I repeat.
Due to an inspection of the school facilities, all of today's afternoon classes and club activities are canceled.
All students are encouraged to leave the school building at once.
What? But we were supposed to have the pool this afternoon!
You pervert! You just wanted to see the girls in swimsuits!
A sudden cancellation?
Huh? What the hell's that?!
Oh, what a surprise! They're dylitklis.
Dyl-what now?
Dylitklis.
They're insects from the 7th dimension of Hearse.
Ah, I see.
Himea, these things don't happen to attack humans, do they?
They do, they're carnivores.
They're really happy since there's so much prey here.
Oh, of course.
Guess I'll have to rough 'em up.
Take this, Shocky Shock attack!
Ah, don't run away!
Oh, so that's how you want it? Then take this!
Ah, I thought I was going to die.
Wait, I actually did die.
But you were still really cool, Taito!
You're late. You'll get the death penalty.
I said I already died!
Woah! What the hell is that?!
Can't you tell? I guess you're as stupid as a monkey after all.
Eat this! This is my finishing blow,
Final Finish Last Shocky Shock Attack!
Ew, what the hell's this?
Did you take care of the insect scum that got out of the room?
I wouldn't be here if I didn't, now would I?
I had the principal send the students home, but I guess that was unnecessary.
Hey, did you see that?
My Shocky Shock was awesome, right?
Hey...
Just what the heck's going on in this school?
Um, for what reason did you summon me?
I'm letting you explain about this school.
You should be grateful.
Huh, you really do act like this towards adults too, don't you?
Anyway,
who is she?
Suzae Saeko.
She's a military officer.
Military, as in the JSDF?
Or from the American army?
Neither.
We're a magic-based organization acting above national level.
Our authority stretches farther than the police, JSDF, and the government's.
The incompetent always try to hide behind authority.
They're working with the people who are after me.
Seriously?!
I love it when you say it like that, Taito.
Huh? But, um...
That means you're wondering if it's true, right?
Yeah.
Then yeah, seriously!
Don't forget that it's thanks to the military's barrier that the Church and Temperon Crowley can't find you here.
Yes, I won't forget.
And I won't forget what the military and Church did to me either.
Taito!
Saitohimea is nothing but a shell by now.
Does the military still want her?
We'll decide whether she holds any value or not.
Taito!
Let me see Taito!
It is of no matter if she holds any value or not.
As a criminal who sided with Bahlskra, she will be sealed in the void for all eternity.
That is the Church's decision.
Himea.
What's wrong, Himea?
Are you feeling sick?
Nah, it's nothing.
You might've noticed already, Kurogane-kun,
but there exist multiple different worlds.
Like the world where the witch, Saitohimea, comes from
and the world of demons like Mirai of Andoh.
Mirai of Andu, Daughter of Indra!
And the demonic plane where Mirai of Andoh, Daughter of Indra comes from.
Those are just two of an innumerable amount of worlds.
The worlds are all connected by dimensional rifts.
You have to go through these rifts in order to reach the other worlds.
All of these dimensions intersect here at Miyasaka High School.
Got it, small fry?
Nope, not at all.
What the hell is this?!
I did call you a monkey, but let me rephrase.
Huh?
You're just a mere flea.
Taito...
The military established Miyasaka High School in order to keep this dimensional intersection under close watch.
Genius = Gekkou
Flea = Immortal-kun
But why build a school?
Genius = Gekkou
Flea = Immortal-kun
Only those under the age of eighteen are able to pass through the rifts.
Genius = Gekkou
Flea = Immortal-kun
We don't know why, but once you pass that age you can no longer traverse the holy ground.
Holy ground?
That's what the military calls the distortions.
The responsibilities of the student council include monitoring the holy ground and eradicating any intruders that might wander in.
And in return, the student council members are free from all student obligations, such as attending class.
The principal and the school's staff are all aware of this.
However, they are not aware of the school's true purpose.
Huh...
The end.
Never ask about it again.
Hey, Gekkou!
If the afternoon classes are canceled, does that mean P.E. is canceled as well?
So we're not going to the pool?
Naturally.
No way! I want to swim!
See? I've prepared for it already!
Oh, she had a swimsuit under it.
You can't do that, Taito!
Hey, Gekkou! Let's go to the pool! Come on!
Let's go!
Taito!
Ouch! Himea!
Himea?
I guess I'll just have to kill every other girl in existence so you won't get distracted.
Um... Can I go yet?
Yahoo!
Gekkou!
Taito!
Isn't that hot?
I more or less understand the circumstances here,
but there's one more thing I want to know.
Why do you have to fight your little twin brother?
He tried to kill me.
I just returned the favor.
That's all.
But that still doesn't mean you can...
It's none of your business.
But...
Why'd you do that?!
This feels great, Gekkou!
Come on in, Taito!
Okay! I'll get it, so stop pulling!
Mirai-chan attack!
Are you trying to kill me?!
But you're Immortal-kun, so it's okay!
O-Okay, then I'll have a go too!
Himea-chan attack!
Himea!
I'm dying!
Let's see who can stay underwater the longest!
I won't lose to you!
Hinata and I...
We were always together.
If we weren't, we would fall apart.
That's what I believed, and I thought Hinata believed the same.
Until that day.
Mom?
Dad?
Oh hey, Nii-san.
You're home early.
Hinata...
Say, can you see this?
Oh, I guess not.
Then I have no use for you, Nii-san.
I should get going.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
I sacrificed Mom and Dad for a nine-year long contract.
Seems like this will be a long journey.
Contract?
Journey?
What does that mean?
I'm letting you live for another nine years.
Nine years?
Enjoy your life up until then.
Hinata!
Wait, Hinata!
Nine years?
It's running out?
My nine years are running out!
Screw that!
Hinata, my inferior little brother, is going to kill me?
That's not even funny! As if I'd let him kill me!
So, you've come here to kill me?
Nope, I came to devour you.
Hinata offered you as a sacrifice to me.
So your life now belongs to me!
So you were a familiar sent by Hinata to kill Gekkou?
Yeah. He summoned me with a magic cirlce.
But Gekkou attacked first,
And pushed me down.
Pushed you down...
Then he stabbed me and stripped me.
Prepare yourself!
I've been ready for a long time now.
You thought I would spend these nine years doing nothing?
You foolish human!
I'll fry you with my lightning!
Exorcise, Spell Error!
Huh? W-Wait a second!
No, I won't!
That's not fair! Time-out!
Silence, small fry!
W-Why...
Why can't I use my power?
Spell Error exorcises all powers.
A small fry like you wouldn't stand a chance.
W-Why can you do something like that?
Because I'm a genius.
Then Gekkou used Spell Error and laid a curse upon me and forced me into a contract.
And what's more, Gekkou has to kiss me to remove the seal.
He's so mean, isn't he?
H-Huh?
Where's Gekkou?
Did I startle you?
Who are you?
Now, who might I be?
Well, that doesn't matter since you're leaving.
Wai- Hold on!
Exorcise, Spell Error!
Just kidding!
Too bad, but that didn't hurt at all.
Spell Error didn't work?!
Oh, just kidding again.
Impossible!
Don't be so impatient, Gekkou-chan.
Hmph. He left without me.
Gekkou you meanie!
Well, I have a message from Hinata for you, Gekkou-chan.
W-We're suddenly alone, huh?
I-
I guess so.
Red rain?
Huh? I suddenly feel kinda dizzy...
Let's go back inside, Taito.
Himea?
Maybe you didn't notice, but you've
already died twice because of this rain.
I thought I killed Hinata with my own hands...
I'll repeat what Hinata said.
"You'd better give up on keeping Saitohimea, Nii-san."
A fool like you won't be able to handle that crazy witch.
Especially if you're doing it to piss me off.
But since you probably won't listen,
I'll give you a little warning if you're still planning to keep her.
Beware of the moon's encroachment.
So that's how it is.
Very well, Hinata,
I'll play along with your little game.
hoppe ni odeko ni fuwafuwa no kissu
Fluffy kisses on my cheeks and forehead.
suki no iwanai kana
Won't you tell me that you love me?
demo nandatte kimochii kiss
Cause your kiss feels great.
marshmallow, chocolate, ice cream
Marshmallows, chocolate, and ice cream.
oyatsu no jikan mata kyou shinai?
Will we drink tea again today?
itatte fuutsu no onnanoko nano desu
I'm a normal girl,
dakedo tsuyoi ko de itaishi
but I want to be a strong girl.
kimi no tokubetsuna ko ni naritai
I wanted to be your special one.
te ashi batabata amaeteru
Flapping my hands and legs like a spoiled child,
tokidoki mukashi na ko desu
sometimes being my old self.
sokkenai kimi hontou wa suki de
The truth is that I love your blunt attitude,
terekakushi de ijiwaru shiteru nante ne
teasing me to hide your embarrassment.
hyakumankai kissushite ne hyaku paasento uketoruyo
If you want to kiss me a million times, I'll accept them for sure.
ganbatte homeraretai
I'll try harder, so you will praise me.
hyakuten manten jyanakutemo
Even if I don't score a 100,
hanamaru kurai kureru kana
at least you'll give me a flower circle.
yoku dekimashita demo ii yo
Saying, "You did great!", would be enough.
kimi de yorokobi kao mietara
Whenever I see your smiling face,
ureshikutte sakenjauyo
I let out a shout of joy!
Hello! It's Mirai!
Um, what was it again?
Erm...
Oh, right! I'm a really powerful demon!
You see, I'm a descendant of this really famous demon!
Mama always told me how great I was!
But Gekkou just calls me a small fry!
I keep telling him that I'm not a small fry though!
But he... Well...
Next time  「The Tenma yet unsung」
Um...
Huh?
What was I saying again?